biddersplace.com 2011-10-08

# Online Auctions - Save upto 95% on Branded Products | BiddersPlace.com »

**1\. General**

BiddersPlace.com is available for visit by anyone at any time without registering.

Any time any website is accessed, standard data such as the URL being accessed, the referring website, and your IP address is sent to the server. We may store this data anonymously for usage tracking and diagnostic purposes. This data will not be shared with any third parties.

In order to participate in auction on BiddersPlace.com, you must create an account. In order to create an account, we will ask you to provide some personal information. This data will be stored on our server and will not be sold or transferred to any third parties.

**2\. Data Collection**

Personal data is the information needed to identify you, for example your name, address, date of birth, e-mail address, etc. With your consent, personal data are recorded and processed by BiddersPlace.com, in particular but no limited to:

  * \- When you first create your account
  * \- When you purchase bids
  * \- When you purchase items you have won on an auction

We collect this data in order to be able to provide you with the services offered on BiddersPlace.com.

**3\. Use of the Data**

The personal data that you have provided will be used to provide the services on BiddersPlace.com. For example, we will use

  * \- Your shipping address to send you items that you have won 
  * \- Billing information to facilitate payments for bids and items 
  * \- Your date of birth to determine that you are of legal age to enter into a binding contract

We ask for your e-mail address so that we can stay in contact with you by e-mail. We reserve the right to occasionally email you in order to:

  * \- Update you on new changes to BiddersPlace.com
  * \- Notify you of changes to Terms and Conditions
  * \- Send receipts whenever you make a payment
  * \- Notify you of new auctions or exciting marketing promotions (if you opted in during signup)

We may utilize service of third parties to perform functions such as payments or email management. We will only share the data that is absolutely necessary in order to perform the needed function. You email will not be sold or shared with third parties for solicitation purposes.

We will not sell or transfer your personal data to third parties, unless required by law.

Upon your consent, when you win an auction we will publish your name, town, state and country of your location as testimonial.

All data is stored securely on our servers.
